TRAGEDY ON THE WAVES
[male staff] Jeez,
just look at all this blood.
If he were anyone else,
I don't think he'd come back here.
[male staff groans]
[slowly] There, now you have
some more melon leaves.
[Legoshi] He's still talking to Melon.
[male staff] I swear, if I have to carry
another dead body out of this place...
So, what do you plan on getting today?
What? Oh, uh... [chuckles]
I mean, I would pick...
[laughs] I think black bunny there
would look good on you.
[Legoshi] Huh? Oh.
Miss Cosmo mentioned a strange pattern.
Could this be it?
[Holger] They suit you better than...
the leopard spots.
Are you afraid?
[Legoshi] What if Melon is transforming
the way my mom did?
- Are you anxious?
- Huh?
- You must feel so alone.
- Hmm.
I guess you have always been alone.
[Legoshi] That's right.
I thought he was a being of pure evil,
but he's still just like anyone else.
If only someone out there
was able to truly understand you.
- [male staff] Have you decided?
- Uh...
Uh... [chuckles nervously] Not yet, no.
Is that right?
The Droplet of the Reaper is nice.
Huh?
What is the Droplet of the Reaper?
[Holger] Someday, I hope you find a way
to heal your broken heart.
[Legoshi] Hmm.
[beeping]
ANTI-CRIME CAMPAIGN
LET'S LIVE TOGETHER
[stage staff] That's good.
Need some tape!
This is an emergency. I need to speak
with the Beastar right away.
Huh? Well, I'm afraid he isn't here.
I heard he'd been seen
on the top floor of the police station.
You heard that... I hope you didn't come
out here on account of some silly rumor.
[receptionist chuckles]
Of course not. That was a joke.
Oh, I see.
I was called here
by the Crime Prevention Department.
Then, may I see your identification?
- Is my student ID all right?
- Sure.
Apparently, some big idol
is going to be here.
Uh-huh.
She's really popular
with the younger generation, so...
Oh, all set.
- Take elevator E to the 38th floor.
- Thank you very much.
Oh, right. By chance, do you know
how many floors does this building has?
108.
Good luck to anyone
who tries to take the stairs, right?
They'd have to be pretty silly
to attempt something like that.
[laughs] They sure would.
[panting heavily]
I need to convince the Beastar.
Fifty-five floors to go.
Can I make it on this leg?
[panting]
[guard 2] Five! And guess who wins!
- You never called last card, though.
- What?
Third place again, eh? [laughs]
[groans] Can I just win once?
[exhales heavily]
Aren't there supposed to be more floors?
[doorknob rattles]
[tense music playing]
Got to remember to thank the Shishi-Gumi.
[door unlocks, opens]
- [alarm beeping]
- Huh?
[guard 1] Fire door on 100th?
I'm happy to go give it a look.
- Put the game on pause for now.
- Hey! Come on now.
[Louis] I can go up from here.
[music ends]
[whirring]
[dings]
I'm on 100. Everything looks clear.
[guard 3 over radio]
Is the system acting up again?
[guard 2] I'll check.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[suspenseful music plays]
- Huh?
- [gasps]
- Hey! Get back here!
- [door locks]
[grunting]
Open this door!
- Hey! [grunting]
- [doorknob rattling]
[thudding]
[guard 2 grunting]
Huh?
[chuckles]
Time to come out, little fawn.
Huh? Come on!
Where did he go?
[groaning]
Uh...
[guard 2 over radio] Intruder alert!
Be on the lookout for a teenage male deer!
[chuckles]
[sighs wearily]
[Gon] A joint drama club?
That's what we'd like you to approve.
Carnivores and herbivores sharing a stage.
Together, we'd rock that meteor festival.
[Gon] I can't approve that.
You two should understand that
better than anyone.
Of course we do.
Last year, our club went through things
nobody should ever have to deal with.
That's why this matters!
FESTIVAL OF THE METEOR
REAPPLICATION FORM
[Els] This is something we need to do!
Carnivores and herbivores together!
- That's why this matters?
- Yes.
Oh.
So, your plan is to perform
Adler the Reaper then?
- Right.
- But why?
Because it's about love between species,
sacrificing yourself
for those you care about.
And for our drama club,
that's a story that means something!
If you're wondering about casting,
we still haven't locked in our Adler yet.
- But we have time to figure that out--
- Enough, stop already.
Is that truly the message
you want to convey?
That true love justifies
throwing your life away?
- [Bill] Uh...
- [Els] Huh?
After experiencing a devouring incident,
you two surely understand.
Death solves nothing
for those left behind.
True. But Adler's a classic.
For us, it's sort of a tradition--
Well, be that as it may,
a separated curriculum is ultimately safer
for everybody involved.
Is it not?
Yeah.
I guess, but...
And do you wish to die as Adler does?
Well, I'd rather not die at all.
[Gon] Hmm.
Even so, you still want
carnivores and herbivores
to work together in this club?
[both] Yes.
Well, why not channel that feeling
into a new play?
[both] What?
I've been thinking,
it's high time for the drama club
to have a new signature play.
A fresh, original script.
[both laugh] Yes, sir!
We'll give it a shot!
[guard] Kines is a narcotic?
That one's rich, kiddo.
- I literally just drank one.
- [gasps]
And I'm feeling pretty great!
[grunts, strains]
[Louis] Is he...
What the hell?
- [groaning, straining]
- It's the Kines reaction. This is bad!
[groaning]
- [snarls]
- [grunts]
- [metal clangs]
[growling]
[straining] Shit!
[both grunting]
[thrilling music playing]
[thudding]
Attempting to eat an herbivore
at a police station is bold,
but it's also very stupid.
[grunts]
You all right?
I take it that you're the Beastar.
Much appreciated.
[Yahya] Hmm.
"KINES IS A DRUG"
THE KINES REPORT
This belong to you?
Yes.
Kines is a dangerous beverage.
It seems this security guard
was a frequent partaker.
If we don't stop it being sold,
these incidents
will keep happening everywhere.
That's what you snuck
into a police station like a spy
to tell me?
- Saving me alone doesn't mean anything.
- Hmm.
You can handle this on your own.
But you're Beastar.
You're able to attack the problem
directly at its root!
I need your help!
- [guard pants]
- [gasps]
[Yahya growls]
[all panting]
[host] Let's move on to the photo session.
- [grunts, groans]
- [host] Please stand in the center first.
- [guard panting]
- [idol] All right.
- [camera shutters clicking]
- Everybody, live together!
[both panting, grunting]
[host] Okay, you ready?
Next, please enter from stage right.
- [idol] Live together!
- [grunts]
- [grunting]
- [screams, gasps]
[idol pants, whimpers]
[guard 2] Take it easy!
[guard 3] Stop it!
- Now's your moment.
- [male] What's going on?
- All right.
- [guard 3] Hold him down!
- [growling]
- [indistinct shouting]
[Louis] It's Kines!
He's under the influence of Kines!
That's what drove him wild.
This security guard
drank one can of Kines,
and it transformed him
into a meat-frenzied beast!
Hey, check it out. Isn't that
The Horns Conglomerate kid?
If not for a stroke of luck,
I only would have left that elevator
in his stomach.
At this very moment, he would be
tearing my flesh, snapping bones.
And this is but one such incident
that Kines is responsible for.
Despite all this,
you can purchase Kines anywhere,
and everyone you know is drinking it.
- You're quite the actor, Louis.
- We can't allow this to go on!
The way you shine in that spotlight,
it's like you were born for it.
Everyone, Kines is a narcotic.
Wow, right out with it.
As a matter of fact,
that's why I came to the station today,
to warn the police of the threat it poses.
- You have any proof of that?
- I do.
And I can present my findings
here and now.
"KINES IS A DRUG"
THE KINES REPORT
[fox] Wait, for real?
That's freaky.
[Legoshi typing] "The Droplet...
of the Reaper."
BREATHTAKING VIEW
THE REAPER'S BLOODDROP
That's not what I expected.
Hmm. I guess even Melon
appreciates beautiful things.
[mouse clicking]
Now, where is it?
Oh, here we go.
[Ogma] Do you realize the ramifications
of your little stunt?
Take a look at this.
GOLDEN HIND HOLDINGS
It's crashing.
I should not need to remind you
that the company that produces Kines
is owned by Azuki's family.
Still, you chose to charge ahead
without thinking about the consequences.
- But I--
- I'm not finished.
Because you chose to make a show
out of what you've done,
you've turned it into a scandal
for the The Horns Conglomerate.
Have you heard what people are saying?
That you deliberately staged
a carnivore attack
to spread the idea
that Kines is dangerous.
If I know that a crime will occur
and I do nothing about it,
I'm an accomplice too!
You want me to stand by and watch?
[Ogma] I'm talking about
how you went about it.
Consider, for one solitary moment,
Azuki's parents.
They just saw their daughter's fiancé
make a spectacle of himself
in far more ways than one.
Is this about my leg?
I never intended to hide it.
[Ogma] Is this some dramatic ploy
to get the wedding called off?
What?
So, what is it, then?
Are you uninterested in women?
Well, that's a fairly significant
change of topic.
I'm simply asking
if it's women in general you dislike or...
if it's just female deer.
Whatever the case, it poses a problem.
[Louis] I think Azuki is
a perfectly wonderful lady.
Do you now?
I had heard that your evening alone
with her came to a rather troubling end.
What's troubling is my father
keeping tabs on my private life.
Who are you even hearing this from?
We're talking as president and successor,
not as father and son.
All right, stand up.
From the moment I first bought you
for seven million,
these sorts of business discussions
became inevitable and essential.
Half a million for your horns,
2.5 million for the leg...
That's ten million
standing in front of me.
Take as many detours as you like,
but I raised you to be the heir
to The Horns Conglomerate.
Don't forget that.
[door opens, closes]
[Legoshi] Hmm.
I've passed by here
on my deliveries before,
but how long has it been
since I looked out at the ocean like this?
[inhales deeply]
That reminds me...
God, I really wish
I could have come out here with Haru.
[breathes deeply]
Though, if she were here next to me,
I'd probably be too focused on her
to even notice the ocean.
I'd probably creep her out.
Still, would have been nice
to talk about life as we took in the view.
We wouldn't even have to talk.
Just having her near would make me happy.
Ah, come to think of it,
I've never gone to the beach
with the guys from room 701.
[chuckles] I'd love to swim with them.
We canines really love the water.
Speaking of water,
someday, I hope Mr. Sagwan
will take me out to the open sea
and show me his homeland.
And Ms. Seven could come too. [chuckles]
That would be so fun, I swear.
[breathes deeply]
You know, I'm actually
a pretty cheerful guy.
Or maybe I'm becoming more cheerful.
Eighteen years.
They've ended up being pretty fun.
Thanks to everyone around me.
But...
as for Melon,
maybe he's always
watching the ocean alone,
hoping to be understood.
I wonder what goes through his mind
as he looks at the Droplet of the Reaper.
If only he and I
could just talk things over.
And those leaf tattoos of his...
[scoffs]
I doubt he wants to show them off,
but I bet they're pretty.
Holger mentioned he was lonely,
that he is alone.
If only he would talk to me,
even just a little bit,
I'm sure we could come to an--
[gunshot]
[Legoshi groans]
What?
[Melon imitates Holger] "Are you afraid?
Are you anxious?
You must feel so alone."
[in normal voice] My soul is laid bare!
I feel like I'm drowning in darkness!
[imitates Holger]
"You must have always been alone."
[in normal voice] Oh, it's so true!
Nobody, nobody understands me
or the things I've been through!
Huh? What?
That close to what you thought
I said in that tattoo parlor?
Oh, thank you! How about this?
You can become the one who finally
cracks my code and understands!
- [gasps in disbelief]
- [laughs maniacally]
Alas. The boy with the leopard mother
and gazelle father is a tragic hero.
A life bereft of love
was his ultimate downfall!
Unable to fully trust the friendly wolf
who tried to believe in him,
our hero ended up killing him
with his very own hands!
Bang!
Oh my, what a tragedy.
Oh, yeah, I have, like,
freakily, abnormally good hearing,
so I picked up on your attempts
to follow me right from the get-go.
Though, I got to admit, the fact that
you're still alive did surprise me.
[Legoshi] It was all a trap!
[suspenseful music playing]
Well, anyway, this little reunion
really is a second chance.
This time, I'll make
extra special sure you die.
So, will you be smashed
upon the jagged rocks
till your body is in bits,
or will your lungs fill
as you drown in the ocean?
[softly] Huh.
But why?
[mutters mockingly]
All I wanted...
- I just wanted us to talk.
- [laughs maniacally]
Oh, my God, you're killing me here!
[mockingly] "It's just... I wanted to talk,
for us to be friends."
[laughs] God damn it, you're hilarious!
You sympathized with me
and thought I'd sympathize with you.
Oh my, you really do live
in a fantasy world, don't you, wolfy boy?
Why are you doing this?
- [snarls]
- [choking]
Just because it's fun.
How can it not be
when someone so full of hope like you
falls right into the death grip
of despair?
Thing is, sympathy is boring.
If you want to touch my heart,
there's only one thing you can do.
When you die,
try to make it messy, would ya?
- It's far more entertaining.
- [choking, grunting]
Scary, huh?
Do you want to know
what my favorite thing in the world is?
[choking]
- The face of someone afraid of death.
- [choking, gasping]
No matter what species they are,
everybody makes the same one without fail.
Not a lie to be found,
a face that's genuinely honest.
[strained] Melon.
[Melon laughs maniacally]
Yes, that's the one!
- That face there.
- [choking]
- [Melon] Oh, oh!
- [Legoshi gasps]
[exhales heavily]
The Droplet of the Reaper, huh?
[sighs]
Better get back to it.
[muffled grunting]
[muffled groaning]
[Melon in distance] Correct!
The concept of meat as we know it
only came into being after the war.
- [Haru sighs]
- [Melon] The war changed everything.
[continues indistinctly]
He still hasn't gotten back to you?
You should break up with him
already, Haru.
- [sighs] Maybe I should.
- There are so many nice guys out there.
- You'll find one in no time.
- [Melon clears throat] You two!
[both gasp]
- Done chatting?
- I'm sorry.
As I was saying,
the relationship between these two groups
began to break down.
They stood on the line
between love and hate.
From there,
complicated emotions began to emerge.
[closing theme song playing]
♪ Just like a new melody ♪
♪ Keep it beating on and on ♪
♪ I don't want to live without it ♪
♪ You give me the strength inside ♪
♪ Some things aren't meant to be ♪
♪ You say it like you know ♪
♪ But I really want you ♪
♪ I want you to see it the way I do ♪
♪ 'Cause every time I think about you ♪
♪ My heartbeat goes a-risin' ♪
- ♪ And I just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till I... ♪
♪ Till I die ♪
♪ There's nothing
That can beat like this ♪
♪ Faster as I close my eyes ♪
- ♪ Just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till the... ♪
♪ Till the night ♪
♪ Now as long as you are here by my side ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ I keep walking on ♪
♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
- ♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
- ♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ I keep walking on ♪